# **Brandon Owens**

#### **Retail Customer Service**

Wilmington, DE - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Brandon-Owens/ead12c2fad562576

A qualified customer service professional with four years in fast-paced customer service and call center environments. Personable and professional under pressure. Seeking a entry level role with room for advancement. Skilled in training staff and establishing rapport with clients. Self-motivated with exceptional communication and computer capabilities.

Retail sales professional versed in product placement and merchandising. Extensive experience in inventory and shipment processing. A retail sales professional offering experience in retail customer service focused on exceeding sales goals. A punctual retail sales professional focused on exceeding expectations and building customer loyalty. Flexible schedule and strong mathematical aptitude. Enthusiastic and outgoing Sales Associate proficient at building positive relationships with new and existing customers by offering superior customer service skills. Areas of experience include sales, customer service, stock and inventory. I am considered patient and empathetic with extensive background in conflict resolution and customer care.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Floater**

Colonial Parking - Wilmington, DE - January 2016 to Present

Fill in for various positions at various locations. Customer service, maintenance and supervisory positions.

#### Sales Associate

Home Depot - Newark, DE - October 2014 to June 2015

Operate cash register and provide customer service.

## **Receiving Support**

Macy's - Wilmington, DE - August 2013 to January 2014

## Responsibilities

- \*Developed positive customer relationships through friendly greetings and excellent service.
- \*Verified that all customers received receipts for purchases.
- \*Organized racks and shelves to maintain the visual appeal of the store.
- \*Stocked shelves and supplies and organized displays.
- \*Prepared sales slips and sales contracts.
- \*Greeted customers and ascertained customers' needs.
- \*Demonstrated use and care of merchandise.
- \*Answered questions regarding the store and its merchandise.
- \*Stacked and piled lumber, boards and pallets.
- \*Verified computations against physical count of stock.
- \*Unloaded cargo from truck with hand trucks and pallet jacks.
- \*Swept floors and stored equipment at the end of each shift.
- \*Loaded and unloaded ship cargo.
- \*Attached identifying tags to containers

#### Sales Associate

7-Eleven - Wilmington, DE - August 2012 to January 2013

Maintained established merchandising standards, including window, sales floor and promotional displays.

- \*Determined customer needs by asking relevant questions and listening actively to the responses.
- \*Answered customer telephone calls promptly and in an appropriate manner.
- \*Communicated clear expectations and goals to each team member.
- \*Cultivated a customer-focused shopping environment by greeting and responding to all customers in a friendly manner.
- \*Fostered a positive work environment by consistently treating all employees and customers with respect and consideration.
- \*Mentored new sales associates to contribute to the store's positive culture.
- \*Followed merchandising guidelines to present visually appealing displays.
- \*Verified that all customers received receipts for their purchases.
- \*Resolved all customer complaints in a professional manner while prioritizing customer satisfaction.
- \*Used time efficiently when not serving customers, including folding clothes and cleaning out fitting rooms.
- \*Educated customers about the brand to incite excitement about the company's mission and values.
- \*Welcomed customers into the store and helped them locate items.
- \*Completed all point of sale opening and closing procedures, including counting the contents of the cash register.
- \*Trained new sales associates each quarter.
- \*Identified potential shoplifters and alerted management.
- \*Alerted customers to upcoming sales events and promotions.
- \*Cleaned and organized the store, including the checkout desk and displays.
- \*Priced merchandise, stocked shelves and took inventory of supplies.
- \*Stocked and replenished merchandise according to store merchandising layouts.
- \*Operated a cash register for cash, check and credit card transactions with?accuracy.
- \*Checked temperatures of freezers, refrigerators, and heating equipment to ensure proper functioning
- \*\*Cleaned and sterilized equipment and facilities
- \*Cleaned garbage cans with water or steam
- \*Worked stations including pizza, omelet, soup, salad, sandwich, and dessert at a busy cafeteria.
- \*Followed all safety and sanitation policies when handling food and beverage to uphold proper health standards.
- \*Routinely cleaned work areas, glassware and silverware throughout each shift.
- \*Developed and maintained positive working relationships with others to reach business goals.

#### **Backroom Team Member**

Target 800 Christiana mall - Newark, DE - August 2011 to September 2012

Provided an elevated customer experience to generate a loyal client?le.

- \*Recommended, selected and helped locate and obtain out-of-stock product based on customer requests.
- \*Answered product questions with up-to-date knowledge of sales and store promotions.
- \*Greeted customers entering the store to ascertain what each customer wanted or needed.
- \*Described product to customers and accurately explained details and care of merchandise.
- \*Politely assisted customers in person and via telephone.
- \*Communicated with vendors regarding back order availability, future inventory and special orders.
- \*Answered product questions with up-to-date knowledge of sales and store promotions.
- \*Effectively communicated with and supported sales, marketing and administrative teams on a daily basis.
- \*Conducted weekly walk-throughs with the manager to discuss interior visual displays, including store window presentation.

- \*Handled daily heavy flow of paperwork and cooperated with the accounting departments on invoicing and shipping problems.
- \*Bagged, boxed or gift-wrapped sold merchandise per customer's request.
- \*Developed reputation as an efficient service provider with high levels of accuracy.
- \*Scored in top 10% of employees in successful resolution of issues
- \*Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathetic manner.
- \*Served as the main liaison between customers, management and sales team.
- \*Ensured superior customer experience by addressing customer concerns, demonstrating empathy and resolving problems on the spot.
- \*Managed wide variety of customer service and administrative tasks to resolve customer issues quickly and efficiently.
- \*Provided ongoing guest service, including giving fashion advice.
- \*Processed [number] daily invoices and billed renewed invoices to clients.
- \*Executed in-season pricing strategies, including promotions and markdowns to reach financial targets of number.
- \*Maintained cleanliness and presentation of stock room and production floor.
- \*Recipient of multiple positive reviews acknowledging dedication to excellent customer service.
- \*Directed calls to appropriate individuals and departments.
- \*Built long-term customer relationships and advised customers on purchases and promotions.
- \*Monitored cash drawers in multiple checkout stations to ensure adequate cash supply.
- \*Helped drive sales goals and achieve monthly guotas.
- \*Organized store merchandise racks by size, style and color to promote visually appealing environment.
- \*Routinely answered customer questions regarding merchandise and pricing.
- \*Operated a POS system to itemize and complete an average of number customer purchases.
- \*Created and maintained an organized database to develop promotional sales.
- \*Dedicated to continuously improving sales abilities and product knowledge.
- \*Achieved sales goals and service performance requirements of \$amount through new customer sales.
- \*Routinely answered customer questions regarding merchandise and pricing.
- \*Designed displays to make the store experience interactive, engaging and reassuring.
- \*Asked open-ended questions to assess customer needs.
- \*Learned, referenced and applied product knowledge information.
- \*Folded and arranged garments in attractive displays.
- \*Communicated all store initiatives and promotions to customers to generate return business.
- \*Set up and explained new membership contracts.
- \*Recommended alternative items if product was out of stock.

#### **Retail Customer Service**

Forever 21 - Newark, DE - April 2011 to September 2011

Partnered with sales representatives and managers to coordinate delivery and merchandising schedule.

- \*Answered customer questions regarding store merchandise, department information and pricing.
- \*Organized store merchandise racks by size, style and color.
- \*Led merchandise selection, pricing, planning and marketing.
- \*Ran markdown reports, managed store replenishment and analyzed buying reports.
- \*Created visual marketing and styled window displays.
- \*Assembled promotional displays, including quarter and full-size point of purchase displays.
- \*Conferred with store managers to obtain information about customer needs and preferences.
- \*Set and recommended mark-up rates, mark-down rates and selling prices for merchandise.
- \*Established strong vendor relationships to maintain and support the business.
- \*Organized racks and shelves to maintain the visual appeal of the store.

- \*Verified that all customers received receipts for purchases.
- \*Developed positive customer relationships through friendly greetings and excellent service.
- \*Demonstrated use and care of merchandise.
- \*Greeted customers and ascertained customers' needs.
- \*Stocked shelves and supplies and organized displays.
- \*Organized racks and shelves to maintain the visual appeal of the store.
- \*Verified that all customers received receipts for purchases.

## Cashier/Customer Service

walmart - New Castle, DE - July 2010 to January 2011

Operated a cash register for cash, check and credit card transactions with?accuracy.

Stocked and replenished merchandise according to store merchandising layouts.

Priced merchandise, stocked shelves and took inventory of supplies.

Cleaned and organized the store, including the checkout desk and displays.

Alerted customers to upcoming sales events and promotions.

Identified potential shoplifters and alerted management.

Trained?new sales associates each quarter.

Completed all point of sale opening and closing procedures, including counting the contents of the cash register.

Handled all customer relations issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies.

Welcomed customers into the store and helped them locate items.

Educated customers about the brand to incite excitement about the company's mission and values.

Followed up with over?customers each week to verify that they were satisfied with purchases.

Verified that all customers received receipts for their purchases.

Followed merchandising guidelines to present visually appealing displays.

Mentored new sales associates to contribute to the store's positive culture.

Fostered a positive work environment by consistently treating all employees and customers with respect and consideration.

Cultivated a customer-focused shopping environment by greeting and responding to all customers in a friendly manner.

Worked with the management team to implement the proper division of responsibilities.

Actively pursued personal learning and development opportunities.

Supervised and directed all merchandise and shipment processing.

Answered customer telephone calls promptly and in an appropriate manner.

Determined customer needs by asking relevant questions and listening actively to the responses.

Maintained established merchandising standards, including window, sales floor and promotional displays.

#### **Customer Service Sales**

Hickory Farms - Newark, DE - November 2009 to January 2010

Answered customer questions about product availability and shipment times.

- \*Recommended new ?products?to customers, resulting in add-on business, and up selling.
- \*Greeted customers in a timely fashion, while quickly determining their needs.
- \*Worked night and weekend shifts during holiday season.
- \*Placed special merchandise orders for customers.
- \*Entered data promptly and efficiently with accuracy?
- \*Referred unresolved customer grievances to designated departments for further investigation.
- \*Responded to all customer inquiries thoroughly and professionally.
- \*Processed cash and credit payments rapidly and accurately.
- \*Documented all customer inquiries and comments thoroughly and quickly.

# **EDUCATION**

# **High School Diploma in General Studies**

Moyer Academy - Wilmington, DE 2008 to 2011

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

#### >Skills

- \*Customer-oriented \*Cash register operations \*Computer literate
- \*POS systems knowledge \*Employee relations
- \*Active listening skills \*Exceptional customer service \*Merchandising
- \*Consistently meets sales goals \*Schedule flexibility \*Opening and closing procedures
- \*Credit card transactions \*Weekend availability \*Shipment processing
- \*Retail sales \*Willing to work late hours \*Natural leader
- \*Energetic, friendly and enthusiastic \*Skilled problem solver \*Training development aptitude
- \*Experience cleaning equipment \*Personable \*Quick learner
- \*Upselling techniques \*Honest, trustworthy and punctual \*Neat and clean in appearance
- \*Stocking \*Retail sales experience \*Able to keep a clean and sanitary work station \*Upselling \*On time and reliable
- \*Able to Push heavy trash carts
- \*Proper product storage
- \*Able to work in continuously-standing position for four or more hours